<resources>
<!-- This is the strings.xml file. It contains the string values used in the app.-->
    <string name="app_name">project1-8-Bit-Whit-new</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="intro">Colorado STEM Ecosystem is a statewide network connecting businesses,
        educators and more to improve STEM education across Colorado.
        Our broad approach to STEM helps students develop the skills they need to succeed.
        Sign up today to get involved!</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="content">Content</string>
    <string name="about_ecosystem">About Ecosystem</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>
    <string name="network">Network</string>
    <string name="mission">Mission</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">Home Fragment</string>
    <string name="content_fragment">Content Fragment</string>
    <string name="about_ecosystem_fragment">About Ecosystem Fragment</string>
    <string name="join_fragment">Join Fragment</string>
    <string name="network_fragment">Network Fragment</string>
    <string name="mission_fragment">Mission Fragment</string>
    <string name="donate_fragment">Donate Fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_fragment">Contact Fragment</string>
    <string name="resources_fragment">Resources Fragment</string>
    <string name="link_to_content_button">Link to Content Button</string>
    <string name="about_stem_heading1">Why STEM Ecosystems?</string>
    <string name="about_ecosystem_text1">Why STEM Ecosystems?In ecology, an
        ecosystem is a diverse community that coexists in a physical environment,
        interacting in balanced ways that support all the organisms. The STEM Ecosystems
        community strives to draw from the scientific idea of ecosystems to represent its
        research-based efforts to build networks for the sharing of resources and expertise
        among leaders from education, business and industry, non-profits, philanthropy,
        and others. You can find out more about the national STEM Learning Ecosystem
        Community of Practice launched in 2015</string>
    <string name="about_stem_heading2">How will the Ecosystem be helpful to me and/or my organization?</string>
    <string name="about_stem_text2">The Colorado STEM Ecosystem is designed so that you can
        customize your involvement to meet your own needs. As of May 2022, there is a statewide Ecosystem,
        but soon there will also be 8 regional hubs and a range of community-driven working groups on a
        range of issues—you can opt in or out of any of these. Each will have its own listserv to
        support group communications.The Colorado STEM Ecosystem is specially designed to support partnerships.
        Possible partnerships include those for: Funding, Grants, Outreach, Volunteering, Research, Workforce Development,
    Mentoring, Employment Opportunities, STEM Events, and Scholarships. </string>
    <string name="about_stem_heading3">Why Join a STEM Ecosystem?</string>
    <string name="about_stem_text3">The importance of joining a STEM Ecosystem in Colorado lies in
        fostering collaboration across economic sectors and geographic regions. Currently, there is
        limited interaction between these sectors, hindering the state ability to solve pressing issues.
        Just as species thrive in ecosystems, communities thrive through strong partnerships. STEM Ecosystems
        facilitate relationships among diverse entities such as pK to 12 districts, out of school providers,
        museums, governments, and businesses. These partnerships enable sharing of STEM education and industry
        advancements, promoting efficient progress and problem solving. Membership is open to all without cost,
        requiring only completion of a membership form. Benefits include visibility on an interactive platform (Kumu),
        where members can share information, and access to a communication channel (Google group) for regular
        updates and collaboration facilitation.</string>
    <string name="join_text2">When you join the Ecosystem, you contribute insights on the state of STEM in each region
        and sector of Colorado and help to ensure your local interests and perspectives are represented.</string>
    <string name="join_membership_direct_text">Clicking this button will direct
        you to the web based membership form.</string>
    <string name="visualization_text">The visualization below represents Colorado STEM Ecosystem members and their connections.
        To protect the privacy of Ecosystem members, the public version of this visualization excludes individual information
        including contacts and personal connections.In growing the Ecosystem, we are actively gathering information on the state
        of STEM in each region and sector of Colorado to ensure local interests and perspectives are represented. The STEM Ecosystem
        is comprised of PreK-12  administrators/educators, STEM programming providers, businesses, industry leaders, post-secondary
        administrators/educators, government workers, professional organizations, non-profits, donors/funders, parents/communities,
        medical/health care professionals, and military personnel, among others. The visualization below is interactive and automatically
        updates to reflect new members of the Ecosystem.</string>
    <string name="contact_text">Janelle M. Johnson, PhD, Colorado STEM Ecosystem 2.0 Director</string>
    <string name="donate_text">Please consider making a donation of any amount to support the vital work of individuals,
    organizations and community groups across the state working hard to ensure all Coloradans have the opportunity to
        pursue their passions and achieve success.</string>
    <string name="contact_text_2">Do not hesitate to reach out to us with any questions, concerns, and/or ideas. We are so
        grateful for your time in joining this important network, and we look forward to collaborating with you.</string>
    <string name="donate_directory_text">Clicking this button will take you to our online donation form.</string>
    <string name="mission_text_body">The Colorado STEM Ecosystem 2.0 (CO STEM) is a statewide grassroots coalition to (1) uplift existing
        successful efforts, and (2) jumpstart cross-sector collaboration to bridge educational and economic needs across Colorado.
        Our definition of STEM is broad, interdisciplinary, and inclusive.Metropolitan State University of Denver agreed to serve as the
        backbone organization for the refresh of the Colorado STEM Ecosystem with the support of Colorado Department of Education,
        Colorado Succeeds, and MindSpark Learning. The Colorado STEM Ecosystem is housed in the Office of Education Solutions within
        the School of Education at MSU Denver. CO STEM is a member of the national STEM Learning Ecosystems Community of Practice
        working to improve access to high-quality STEM learning for all students. Launched in September 2015 by the STEM Funders Network,
        the initiative empowers communities to create systemic change that ensures more students develop the STEM knowledge and skills
        they need to learn and thrive in today’s world. When you join the Ecosystem, you contribute insights on the state of STEM in each
        region and sector of Colorado and help to ensure your local interests and perspectives are represented. Please disseminate this website
        among your networks and encourage them to join. Information from the membership form populates an online interactive visualization that
        you can use to support your own networking. A few optional questions ask for data that will be aggregated to highlight important trends
        and priorities of the Ecosystem–those questions are noted on the form. Do not hesitate to reach out to us with any questions, concerns,
        and/or ideas. We are so grateful for your time in joining this important network, and we look forward to collaborating with you.
        The STEM Ecosystem is comprised of businesses, industries, policy makers, STEM programming providers, post-secondary administrators/educators,
        government agencies, professional organizations, trade associations, chambers of commerce, non-profits, donors, funders, philanthropists,
        families, communities, medical and health care professionals, military personnel, and PreK-12 administrators/educators, among others.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>